Guide to the John A. Wilkinson, Secretary of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Phone logs, appointment books, and confidential records, 1932-1987; Accession 1988-A-008
  - Corporation Residences Committee
    - 31 Hillhouse Avenue, 1932-1986 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - 33 Hillhouse Avenue, 1980-1986 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - 35 Hillhouse Avenue, 1953-1986 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - 37 Hillhouse Avenue, 1921-1979 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - 43 Rillhouse Avenue, 1978-1986 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - 47 Hillhouse Avenue, 1920-1967 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - 35 and 43 Hillhouse Avenue, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - 55 Hillhouse Avenue, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - 87 Trumbull Street, 1941-1986 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - University-owned Residences, 1974-1985 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Officers" Houses Budget, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - General, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 37 - 38)
    - General, 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 39 - 40)
  - Personal
    - BVA Steering Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - CARP, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Center for Jewish Life at Yale Committee, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Chamber of Commerce Ad Hoc Economic Development Committee, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Chamber of Commerce Board, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Class of 1960, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Class of 1960 25th Reunion, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Dean of Undergraduate Affairs Appointment, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Development and Alumni Affairs Appointment, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 50 - 51)
    - Friday Group Agendum, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Germantown Friends School Appointment, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 53 - 55)
    - Green Restoration Committee, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Harvard's 300th Anniversary Program, ad from (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Hopkins Grammar School Appointment, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - New Haven Development Commission, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - New Haven Economic Development Plan. Corn., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - New Haven Legal Assistance Board, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - New Haven P.I.L.O.T. Revenue Lobbying Committee, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Recommendations A - K (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Recommendations L - Z (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - St. Martin de Porres Board, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - St. Thomas More Corporation, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Secretaryship Appointment, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 67 - 68)
    - Stiles, Ezra, College Fellowship, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Speeches, 1966-1987 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - U. S. Repeating Arms Task Force, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - United Way, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - United Way Major Firms Unit, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Walpole Library Board, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Yale-China Association, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Y-NHH Board, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Y-NBH Nominating Committee, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Y-NH Medical Center, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Y-NH Medical Center Zoning Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Henry Chauncey and John Wilkinson Appointment Books, 1978-1987 (Box 10, Folder 80 - 89)
  - Copy of chart of Republic of Amalfi presented to Secretary of the University, John A. Wilkinson, by the mayor of Amalfi, 1984 December (Box 1-F)
  - First page of Yale Daily News, 1967 Nov 8, given to Strobe Talbott (then News Chairman) on the occasion of his retirement as an Alumni Fellow of the Yale Corporation (2 copies), 1982 June 18 (Box 1-F)
- Proposals for a new presidential collar, 1981; Accession 1988-A-019
  - Mary Ann Scherr's and Robert Ebendorf's designs for the President's collar. (Box AF10)
- Records, 1970-1986; Accession 1989-A-016
  - A: General Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Personnel: Review Board, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Admissions: general, 1977-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 5)
  - Affirmative Action, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AGB (Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges), 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alcohol, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Fund, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Art Gallery, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Athletics
    - Football, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - General, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Golf, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Women's Gymnastics Team, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - A.Y.A. (Association of Yale Alumni), 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - B: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Band, Yale, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Berkeley College, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - British Art Center, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Budget Committe, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - BandG Committee (Buildings and Grounds), 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 25 - 26)
  - C: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Calendar Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 28 - 31)
  - Campus Mail, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Cardiovascular Pavillion, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Career Services, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chaplain's office, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Charities Drive, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - China, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Commencement: Baccalaurate, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Comptroller's office, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Council, Yale College, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Council of Masters, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 41 - 44)
  - Campus Police, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 45 - 48)
  - CCIC (Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges), 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - CCIC -- BHE (Board of Governors for Higher Education), 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - CSR (Community and State Relations)
    - A - R, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 51 - 52)
    - S - Z, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Arbitration, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Dixwell Community House, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Golf, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Legislation, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - New Haven Symphony, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Nuclear Matters, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Pilot, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Revenue Commission, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Taxes, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Woolsey Hall, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Alumni Fellow Nominating Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Alumni Fellow Percentage Voting, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Corporation, miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Former Corporation Members (Removed to end of collection), 1974-1985 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - D: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Deaths, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - E: General Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Edwards, Jonathan College, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Eleven o'clock meeting, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - F: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Faculty Appointments, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - Financial Aid, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - Foreign Students and Scholars, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - Friday Group, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 106 - 107)
  - Funeral/Memorial Service Programs, 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 108)
  - G: General Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - Gays/Lesbians, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - General Council Office, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - German Visits, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 112)
  - ABG (Giamatti) Dinner Planning Committee, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 113)
  - Giamatti, A. Bartlett, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 114)
  - Graduate and Professional, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 115)
  - H: General Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 116)
  - Havemeyer, Loornis, 1917(1971)-1977 (Box 15, Folder 117)
  - Hillel, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 119)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 121)
  - Human Relations Counselors, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 122)
  - I: General Correspondence, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 123)
  - Inauguration, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 124)
  - Information Office, Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 125)
  - Italian Art Restoration, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 126)
  - J: General Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - K: General Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 128)
  - L: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - Law School, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 130)
  - Lee, R.C., 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 131)
  - Library, Sterling, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 132)
  - M: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 134)
  - Mac - Mc: General, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 135)
  - Mail Log, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 136 - 137)
  - Medicine, School of, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 138)
  - Minority Advisory Council, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 140)
  - N: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 141)
  - New York City Yale Club, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 142)
  - North Haven Mall, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 143)
  - Nuts and Sluts, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 144)
  - O: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 145)
  - P: General Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 146)
  - Peabody Museum, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 147)
  - Personnel Office, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 148)
  - Picketing, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 149)
  - Pierson College, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 150)
  - Q: General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 151)
  - R: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 152)
  - S: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 154)
  - Schmidt, Benno C., 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 155)
  - Science Park, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 156 - 157)
  - Search Committee For ABG (Giamatti), 1985 (Box 20, Folder 158)
  - Search for Chaplain, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 159)
  - Sheffield Scientific School, 1977-1985 (Box 21, Folder 160 - 161)
  - Silliman Lectures, 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 162)
  - South Africa, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 163 - 164)
  - South Africa, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 165)
  - South African Trip, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 166)
  - Summer Programs, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 167)
  - T: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 168)
  - Teacher Preparation Program, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 169)
  - Terry Lectureship Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 170)
  - U: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 171)
  - Union, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 172 - 173)
  - Union, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 174 - 178)
  - United Way: Yale Campaign, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 179)
  - University Council, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 180)
  - V: General Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 181)
  - Violent Crime Policy, 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 182)
  - W: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 183)
  - Weekly Bulletin and Calendar, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 184)
  - XYZ: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 185)
  - Yale China Association, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 186)
  - Yale College Dean's Office, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 187)
  - Yale Co-op, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 188)
  - Yale Name, Protection of, 1984-1986 (Box 25, Folder 189)
  - Yale Psychiatric Institute, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 190 - 191)
  - Y-NH Health Services Corporation, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 192)
  - Y-NHH (Yale New Haven Hospital)
    - Board and Board Members Lists, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 193 - 195)
    - Medical Center, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 196)
    - Medical Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 197)
    - Nominating Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 198)
  - Restricted materials (Box 27)
- Records, 1949-1987; Accession 1989-A-022
  - A - Z, General Correspondence, 1974-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 43)
  - Community and State Relations, General A - Z, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 44 - 45)
  - Admissions File, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Alumni Affairs Commission Report, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Athletics Commission Report, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Council on Priorities and Planning, 1949-1987 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Deaths, 1984-1987 June (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Inauguration, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - ROTC, 1969-1986 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Police Reports, 1986 September-1987 June (Box 2, Folder 53 - 54)
  - Security Committee Reports
    - 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Security Committee Minutes and Agendum, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 57 - 58)
  - Security Surveys, 1984-1987 July (Box 2, Folder 59 - 60)
  - Science Park Development Corp., 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 61 - 64)
  - Two Twelve Assoc. Proposal for Yale Sign Program, 1979-1986 (Box 2, Folder 65 - 66)